[Click here for Breaking News on how Surgence™ is Collaborating with Mayo Clinic to Innovate the Healthcare Supply Chain](https://www.concordancehealthcare.com/blog/rush-university-system-for-health-rush-advances-its-supply-chain-with-surgence-0?hs_preview=prCMxtpa-171272934715)

* * 

    * 

    * 

* * 

    * 

    * 

* * 

    * 

* * 

    * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * 

* * .svg)

Privacy Policy
==============

Concordance Healthcare Solutions Terms of Use

This privacy notice discloses how Concordance Healthcare Solutions collects and uses website visitor and customer  
information. It will notify you of the following:  
  
• What personally identifiable information is collected from our website(s), how it is used and with whom it may be  
shared  
• What choices are available regarding the use of your data  
• The security procedures in place to protect your information  
This Privacy Policy is governed by our Terms of Use.  
  
INFORMATION COLLECTION  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on our website(s). We only have access to/collect information that  
you voluntarily give us via email, online forms and other direct and voluntary contact. Unless you ask us not to, we may  
contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products, new solutions or services or changes to this  
privacy policy. We use your data to provide and improve your customer experience and service. By using our services,  
you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.  
  
CUSTOMER INFORMATION  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time as well as the following:  
• See what data we have about you, if any  
• Change/correct any data we have about you  
• Request that any data we have about you be removed or deleted  
• Express any concern you have about our use of your data  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via our company website(s),  
your information is not stored. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific task or job (for example,  
billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which  
we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.  
If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy, please refer to the Contact Us page. We welcome  
your suggestions and feedback.  
  
CREDIT CARD AND BANK INFORMATION  
Concordance Healthcare Solutions places premium importance on protecting information transmitted via our  
website(s) and will take security precautions to protect all such information however, Concordance Healthcare Solutions  
cannot guarantee that any electronic commerce is completely secure. Concordance Healthcare Solutions will take  
measures to secure and protect all customer-specific information from loss, misrepresentation or misuse and alteration.  
The information collected by Concordance Healthcare Solutions may include shipping information and credit card  
details. Concordance Healthcare Solutions does not store credit card details when processing product orders.  
Concordance Healthcare Solutions web server(s) collect general data pertaining to every website visitor, including the  
IP address, domain name, length of time spent on website page(s) and the pages accessed while visiting our website(s).  
This information is collected to, among other things, aggregate statistical information, facilitate system administration,  
assist the overall customer experience and improve the content of our website(s). Concordance Healthcare Solutions  
may also retain the content of the communications that are sent to Concordance Healthcare Solutions customer  
service representatives. This information helps Concordance Healthcare Solutions to improve and respond to inquiries  
regarding our website(s).  
  
RELEASE OF DATA  
Concordance will never release, sell or give any customer’s information to any other party or organization without the  
customer’s explicit permission unless we are required to do so by law or in cases of necessity as listed below:  
1\. To comply with the law or with legal process  
2\. To protect and defend our rights and property  
3\. To protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Concordance Healthcare Solutions website(s)  
4\. To protect the personal safety or property of our customers, employees or the public  
We use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information  
with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, ex. to ship an order.  
In the event someone supplies false registration information or attempts to pose as someone else, information about  
you – including your computer's IP address -- may be disclosed as part of any investigation into these actions.  
  
THIRD PARTY LINKS  
Website visitors should be aware that this privacy policy only governs the Concordance Healthcare Solutions  
website(s)and the Concordance Healthcare Solutions App. This policy is not applicable to sites accessible via links from  
our website(s). Other external sites unaffiliated with Concordance Healthcare Solutions may collect data or solicit  
personal information pursuant to policies that are not consistent with our Privacy Policy. For this reason, we strongly  
urge caution and remember to seek out individual privacy policies governing any sites you visit.  
  
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY  
Concordance Healthcare Solutions reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy.  
Please refer to the “Contact Us” page for contact information to address any questions or concerns.  
  
HIPAA PRIVACY NOTICE  
In certain circumstances, Concordance Healthcare Solutions is subject to HIPAA privacy and security rules. Click here to  
read or download the Concordance Healthcare Solutions HIPAA Privacy Notice for information regarding our handling of  
protected health information when HIPAA applies.  
  
CALIFORNIA COMPLIANCE DECLARATION  
Concordance Healthcare Solutions adheres to applicable statutes and regulations affecting the healthcare industry in  
the state of California. We declare that Concordance Healthcare Solutions complies with the requirements of §§  
119400-119402 of the California Health and Safety Code. Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California  
residents have the right to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties  
for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to \[title\] at: \[contact\].  
  
CHILDREN  
Concordance Healthcare Solutions website is not intended for use by children under the age of 18.  
We do not knowingly collect or store any personal information from children under the age of 18. We encourage  
parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be fully familiar with the online services used by  
their children. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child under 18 has provided us with information  
without his or her consent, he or she should contact us using our “Contact Us” page. As required by law, we will delete  
such information from our files within a reasonable time.  
  
PRIVACY RIGHTS OF NON-U.S. RESIDENTS  
As noted in our Terms of Use, this website is hosted and operated in the United States, and is not intended to target  
E.U. and other non-U.S. residents. Use of this website will result in transfer of information to Concordance Healthcare  
Solutions in the United States. If you have nevertheless opted to access this site from outside the United States, this  
Privacy Policy will apply to personal information that Concordance Healthcare Solutions collects, uses, and distributes.  
Should you have questions or concerns regarding your personal information, or to make a data subject request regarding  
your personal information please contact us using our “Contact Us” page.  
37435675.1  
®  
1  
  
CONCORDANCE HEALTHCARE SOLUTIONS PRIVACY POLICY  
This privacy notice discloses how Concordance Healthcare Solutions collects and uses website visitor and customer  
information. It will notify you of the following:  
• What personally identifiable information is collected from our website(s), how it is used and with whom it may be  
shared  
• What choices are available regarding the use of your data  
• The security procedures in place to protect your information  
This Privacy Policy is governed by our Terms of Use.  
  
INFORMATION COLLECTION  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on our website(s). We only have access to/collect information that  
you voluntarily give us via email, online forms and other direct and voluntary contact. Unless you ask us not to, we may  
contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products, new solutions or services or changes to this  
privacy policy. We use your data to provide and improve your customer experience and service. By using our services,  
you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.  
  
CUSTOMER INFORMATION  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time as well as the following:  
• See what data we have about you, if any  
• Change/correct any data we have about you  
• Request that any data we have about you be removed or deleted  
• Express any concern you have about our use of your data  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via our company website(s),  
your information is not stored. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific task or job (for example,  
billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which  
we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.  
If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy, please refer to the Contact Us page. We welcome  
your suggestions and feedback.  
  
CREDIT CARD AND BANK INFORMATION  
Concordance Healthcare Solutions places premium importance on protecting information transmitted via our  
website(s) and will take security precautions to protect all such information however, Concordance Healthcare Solutions  
cannot guarantee that any electronic commerce is completely secure. Concordance Healthcare Solutions will take  
measures to secure and protect all customer-specific information from loss, misrepresentation or misuse and alteration.  
The information collected by Concordance Healthcare Solutions may include shipping information and credit card  
details. Concordance Healthcare Solutions does not store credit card details when processing product orders.  
Concordance Healthcare Solutions web server(s) collect general data pertaining to every website visitor, including the  
IP address, domain name, length of time spent on website page(s) and the pages accessed while visiting our website(s).  
This information is collected to, among other things, aggregate statistical information, facilitate system administration,  
assist the overall customer experience and improve the content of our website(s). Concordance Healthcare Solutions  
may also retain the content of the communications that are sent to Concordance Healthcare Solutions customer  
service representatives. This information helps Concordance Healthcare Solutions to improve and respond to inquiries  
regarding our website(s).  
  
RELEASE OF DATA  
Concordance will never release, sell or give any customer’s information to any other party or organization without the  
customer’s explicit permission unless we are required to do so by law or in cases of necessity as listed below:  
1\. To comply with the law or with legal process  
2\. To protect and defend our rights and property  
3\. To protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Concordance Healthcare Solutions website(s)  
4\. To protect the personal safety or property of our customers, employees or the public  
We use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information  
with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, ex. to ship an order.  
In the event someone supplies false registration information or attempts to pose as someone else, information about  
you – including your computer's IP address -- may be disclosed as part of any investigation into these actions.  
  
THIRD PARTY LINKS  
Website visitors should be aware that this privacy policy only governs the Concordance Healthcare Solutions  
website(s)and the Concordance Healthcare Solutions App. This policy is not applicable to sites accessible via links from  
our website(s). Other external sites unaffiliated with Concordance Healthcare Solutions may collect data or solicit  
personal information pursuant to policies that are not consistent with our Privacy Policy. For this reason, we strongly  
urge caution and remember to seek out individual privacy policies governing any sites you visit.  
  
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY  
Concordance Healthcare Solutions reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy.  
Please refer to the “Contact Us” page for contact information to address any questions or concerns.  
  
HIPAA PRIVACY NOTICE  
In certain circumstances, Concordance Healthcare Solutions is subject to HIPAA privacy and security rules. Click here to  
read or download the Concordance Healthcare Solutions HIPAA Privacy Notice for information regarding our handling of  
protected health information when HIPAA applies.  
  
CALIFORNIA COMPLIANCE DECLARATION  
Concordance Healthcare Solutions adheres to applicable statutes and regulations affecting the healthcare industry in  
the state of California. We declare that Concordance Healthcare Solutions complies with the requirements of §§  
119400-119402 of the California Health and Safety Code. Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California  
residents have the right to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties  
for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to \[title\] at: \[contact\].  
  
CHILDREN  
Concordance Healthcare Solutions website is not intended for use by children under the age of 18.  
We do not knowingly collect or store any personal information from children under the age of 18. We encourage  
parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be fully familiar with the online services used by  
their children. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child under 18 has provided us with information  
without his or her consent, he or she should contact us using our “Contact Us” page. As required by law, we will delete  
such information from our files within a reasonable time.  
  
PRIVACY RIGHTS OF NON-U.S. RESIDENTS  
As noted in our Terms of Use, this website is hosted and operated in the United States, and is not intended to target  
E.U. and other non-U.S. residents. Use of this website will result in transfer of information to Concordance Healthcare  
Solutions in the United States. If you have nevertheless opted to access this site from outside the United States, this  
Privacy Policy will apply to personal information that Concordance Healthcare Solutions collects, uses, and distributes.  
Should you have questions or concerns regarding your personal information, or to make a data subject request regarding  
your personal information please contact us using our “Contact Us” page.

### Download Our App

\* for current customers

### Who We Serve

### About

### Corporate Headquarters

85 Shaffer Park Drive  
Tiffin, OH 44883

© 2024 Concordance Health Solutions • All rights reserved • [Privacy](https://www.concordancehealthcare.com/privacy-policy) • [Terms](https://www.concordancehealthcare.com/terms-of-use)
